I'll give you the Miz. I can't believe you like me now.
You're more than a word. You're you.
Every time I see you
I hear the echo
Love bites me
Oh, that was fun.
Why don't you eat your dinner?
Kimi and love. I'll say it again and again.
But, Rioka, you know, the oshiko is popular.
I want you to sing Idol.
I don't want it!
You sing.
Usually?
Usually.
Usually, what?
Idol?
If that's the case, I'd try to turn it off at number 1 or something, and aim for this area.
Sure!
If it looks good enough, ask him if it's that one,
Then we'll turn it off here.
I'll aim a little lower.
Come on, words are reason above all else.
I'll still let you do what you want.
No one more than anyone else.
I can pull with anyone.
Idol
Existence is not shown
Someone more than anyone
Call out to them
Singing casually
Somewhere you can hear them
I hear your voice.
I hear it somewhere
Idols
We found each other, pretending to be each other, same sky
I made the shining light flashOf shining light flashing on and off
Far, far away
Unstoppable, erasable scars
You'll see it too
You can see it.
My prayers
I'm covered again!
Hey, you were too high.
Too high.
Everything's changing weather
It's as if clouds are dancing from the sky
Under the flowers that reveal themselves in the night sky
Give me a memory.
I would be the one
Bloom and shine in this sky
Be the first
Be number one.
Oh, man.
Three hours.
It's tiring, isn't it?
That's exhausting.
Three hours.
Let's sing.
If we can sing...
If you can't sing
Let the windless music reach more people
I don't dream
You are tomorrow
You tomorrow
With you, I'll be a fool
Why is it fun?
I want to have it
When?
When?at some time or another
Somewhere
Lovely.
Let's go dream
Let's go dream.
What do you think of this place?
Oh, I see.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Whoa!
It's gone!
Yes!
Eighty-five points and you're home.
Miss Sparkles.
Darling.
Thank you so much for today.
I'm in tears, but I'm smiling
Nod your head
Take good care of me
I'm thinking of you
Smile.
Give me a good night
Then look down at me
And there you are next to me.
I don't like it.
You're sitting on the floor, doubting me
Then you look down at me
Dropping tears
I hope to live once
Aaaaahhh!!!!
I'm so happy!
WOW!!!
Kan-chan's, sorry!
Aaahhh!!!
I've only heard of 2 of them until Yogu-chan!
me
anaana
Filmin number...
I don't know, I don't know.
You're too close to me.
You're too close, I can't tell you.
We don't even know if we're in love
We're so close, we don't even know if we're in love.
Oh! I got it!
I got it!
Mix, mix, mix.
Mix, mix, mix, mix.
What the hell was that almost spiked just now?
Did you just get here?
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
The project I want to do is...
Chisato Moritaka.
17 years old in a mini skirt.
I'm making it.
Yes, I'm going to cut the barley.
I wanted to confirm our love on the empty sea.
I wanted to make sure of our love... so I slipped my arms around you.
I was running along the water, so bright, I couldn't breathe.
Come and get me. Come and get me.
I'm telling you now that I know you love me.
Congratulations!
Yay!
Thank you.
Everybody rich.
Everybody's rich.
We're all rich.
Let's all go home with this.
Let's all work hard.
I'm hungry. I'm really hungry.
I'm really hungry.
I'm starving.I'm hungry.
Kyuny, I think I can go!
Ooh!
Kyuny!
Chingy!
Let's see, whoosh! Let's get the starting
Start the music!
♪ I believe in you, I'm a colonelongi, but I'm on the clock ♪
# Comissoir
Okay, can you do it?
You got 80 seconds.
Okay, here we go.
Whoo!
Yeah!
I'm in!
Let's go!
Laughing.
Congratulations!
Yeah!
Yay!
We stayed behind to protect and serve.
It's not good.
Kana-chan, we're all going to eat just by looking at you.
Let's eat.
Ha-ha-ha.
Cute.
So cute!
Cute, Kyun.
Cute!
So cute!
Let's smile anytime
I'll make you look at me, even if you look at my words
Deep in the sun, I'm inviting you
Saying I'm free under the skyHe says we're free under the sky.
gentlemen
team
ni
It's too hard.
I'm going to listen in the back.
It's just singing.
Oh! Okay!
Aye-ayo!
I'm coming!
Thank you!
All my underwear...
Oh, yeah!
Is that right?
Yes!
That's right!
The future always paints a picture as gently as I wish it to, when my dreams come true...
I wonder if there's love
There's the sky with you
Or the sky with you
I don't know... Is that it?
No. What do you think?
I like this one. It's cool.
Ha!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
That's an emotional aftertaste.
Wow!
This is so cool.
This is so cool!
That's awesome!
Bingo!
That's awesome!That's great!!!
I'm so happy!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Let's go home together.
We're all going home together!
Oh, my God.
I love you. I love you so much. I can hardly breathe.
I love you so much, I can hardly breathe.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Life's not so bad, is it?
Look at you, you're so melancholy.
I have a feeling you and I could make love somewhere.
I have a hunch
Free tude
It's a freeitude, too.
It's a little bird
It's a song by Nana Ashitama
With 100 points.
Too cute.
♪♪
Now, here comes the last song!
Stardee!
♪♪
Mike of lotion!
He's so cute.
I love it.
I like it.
Oh, yeah.
♪♪
Come on. Come on.
Come on, please.
Come on, please.Please!
83!
It's too weak!
Sometimes it's not as spectacular as it was before.
Sometimes it's not that spectacular because you're swinging twice.
At the moment of 87! I was like, "Oh, my God!
Handwritten bingo karaoke, the successes were,
Haruto Nagamatsu and Boat Sasaki!
It was Hime, the princess.
I was told that my writing style was a bit stupid.
I'll keep thinking about it.
Sakuma-san, if you have this project with leeks, please do it!
Please do!
Well, so I'll leave it at that.
It was interesting, wasn't it? How was it?
It was good, wasn't it?
No, it was a very okay oral reading.
So, really, Natsume is the way to write.
People in their 70s don't often sing karaoke, do they?
You don't sing karaoke in your 70s?
No, I don't.
You just wrote "70s"?
Really?
76 and 100 are the same.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
That's the hardest one.
Well, then, revenge, please.
No, please.
Please, please, please, please.
Well, well, well.
No, but that's good.
Good, good, good.
It was the perfect time for Sasaki and Nakamatsu.
That was great.
Amazing.
I had a job before this day.I was probably working the other day.
I had not eaten much for lunch.
I hadn't even had lunch that much.
I didn't have lunch until 10:00.
Why shouldn't I eat lunch?
It's not good to eat.
Because 1:00 and 2:00 are asses.
Oh, so that's why.
Oh, so that's why...
Because you have to be loud and clear.
You scared the shit out of me, manager.
I was surprised, really.
So you were, manager.
How was the NGT song? Sasaki's song...
Well, it's the best among NGT's songs.
It's called NGT's national anthem.
It's a song that I'm very attached to.
I was happy that she sang it.
And the fact that she decided to sing it at the end...
Anyway, it was fun.
That's for sure.
I'm really grateful.
We did it with all the members.
That's for sure.
Mr. Sasaki, how about doing it with different members?
Oh, I'd like to do it with different members.
With different members.
I'd like everyone to do their best.
With different members...
I feel like we're all biting our tongues.
But they're good, aren't they?
How can I do it after seeing this?
I want to go with Mr. Sakama.
I'm a terrible singer.
I'm just a bad singer.
I won the Meiji commercial.It was a commercial win for Meiji.
I'll definitely do this again in the future.
That's all for now.
This is the Handwritten Bingo Karaoke Project.
Thank you for watching until the end!
Ko le ha!
Thank you very much!
Yo!
I'll be glad to see you.
please